* 

Legal Information
=================

### Legal Information

**WohlSoft team** - is an independent community, and the community is not affiliated with any commercial companies.

Most of provided contents here is made by various community members and available for free download and may be licensed differently.

Some copyrighted stuff which can be found here are property of their respective owners. All their rights are reserved.  
If you think that something provided here does violating of your copyright, feel free report us about them, we will remove your stuff from the public.

All provided content extends by 'as-is' basis, and we are takes no responsibility for damages caused by any of the content which taken from here.

In case of violations of legislations, the community stuff doesn't bear responsibility for violations of some users.

Any advertisement is completely forbidden within the project. **We don't and will don't provide any advertising space!**

If you have any questions or requests to us, feel free to **[contact us](https://wohlsoft.ru/contacts/)**

### Privacy Policy

We are a free community of developers, graphical designers, musicians and ordinary people. We work for creativity, fun and entertainment. **We don't need for any of your personal data.**

Our applications do _never collect any statistics, do never collect any personal data and do never send any data into network without permission of user_. If you figured that any of our applications do send any data into network without your request (for example, launching of network games, launching of shared editing server, usage of Custom graphics online Catalogues, etc.) you should check them and your computer in addition for possible malware infection with your Antivirus because it would be infected and virus would infect our applications too!

**WohlSoft Forums/Wiki.** To register and login to one of our services we don't collect any personal data, but you should give us a real e-mail address by spam protection reasons. _If you don't want to give your personal e-mail address, feel free to register new on any mail servers_. If you sent us any of your personal data yourself, we care about saving them in secret. We don't publish any personal data without of any permissions of owner(s). We will remove any of your exists personal data by your request.

We use cookie files with forums ([read privacy policy of forums](https://wohlsoft.ru/forum/ucp.php?mode=privacy)) and Wiki (MediaWIKI) to remember session key and other some settings like currently switched language.

Copyright © 2014-2024 By Moondust Team

• [Legal information and privacy policy](https://wohlsoft.ru/legal.php) • [About us](https://wohlsoft.ru/about.php) •
